export const musica = [
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20French%20artist%2Fband%20is%20known%20for%20playing%20on%20the%20midi%20instrument%20%22Launchpad%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Madeon",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Daft%20Punk%20",
"Disclosure",
"David%20Guetta"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20had%20hits%20in%20the%2070s%20with%20the%20songs%20%22Lonely%20Boy%22%20and%20%22Never%20Let%20Her%20Slip%20Away%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Andrew%20Gold",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Elton%20John",
"Leo%20Sayer",
"Barry%20White%20"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20is%20the%20best%20selling%20artist%20of%20all%20time%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Beatles",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Michael%20Jackson",
"Elton%20John",
"Elvis%20Presley"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20is%20the%20founder%20and%20leader%20of%20industrial%20rock%20band%2C%20%27Nine%20Inch%20Nails%27%3F",
"correct_answer": "Trent%20Reznor",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Marilyn%20Manson",
"Robin%20Finck",
"Josh%20Homme"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20had%20a%201976%20hit%20with%20the%20song%20%27You%20Make%20Me%20Feel%20Like%20Dancing%27%3F",
"correct_answer": "Leo%20Sayer",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Elton%20John",
"Billy%20Joel",
"Andy%20Gibb"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20an%20album%20released%20by%20The%20Beatles%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Wall",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Abbey%20Road",
"Magical%20Mystery%20Tour",
"Revolver"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "According%20to%20a%20Beatles%20song%2C%20who%20kept%20her%20face%20in%20a%20jar%20by%20the%20door%3F",
"correct_answer": "Eleanor%20Rigby",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Loretta%20Martin",
"Molly%20Jones",
"Lady%20Madonna"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20popular%20rock%20band%20has%20a%20one-armed%20drummer%3F",
"correct_answer": "Def%20Leppard",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Beatles",
"Lynyrd%20Skynyrd",
"Foreigner"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20wrote%20the%20musical%20composition%2C%20%22Rhapsody%20In%20Blue%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "George%20Gershwin",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Irving%20Berlin",
"Duke%20Ellington",
"Johnny%20Mandel"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20singer%20was%20featured%20in%20Swedish%20producer%20Avicii%27s%20song%20%22Wake%20Me%20Up%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Aloe%20Blacc",
"incorrect_answers": [
"John%20Legend",
"CeeLo%20Green",
"Pharrell%20Williams"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Irish%20musician%20Hozier%20released%20a%20music%20track%20in%202013%20titled%2C%20%22Take%20Me%20to%20______%22",
"correct_answer": "Church",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Mosque",
"Synagogue",
"Temple"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20one%20of%20these%20artists%20appears%20in%20the%20album%20Deltron%203030%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dan%20the%20Automater",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Lamarr%20Kendrick",
"Danger%20Mouse",
"CeeLo%20Green"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20artists%20do%20NOT%20originate%20from%20France%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Chemical%20Brothers",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Air",
"Justice",
"Daft%20Punk"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "EDM%20producer%20Marshmello%20performs%20live%20wearing%20clothes%20and%20a%20marshmallow%20mask%20of%20what%20colour%3F",
"correct_answer": "White",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Black",
"Blue",
"Yellow"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20artists%20was%20NOT%20a%20member%20of%20the%20electronic%20music%20supergroup%20Swedish%20House%20Mafia%2C%20which%20split%20up%20in%202013%3F",
"correct_answer": "Alesso",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Steve%20Angello",
"Sebastian%20Ingrosso",
"Axwell"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%201952%20musical%20composition%204%2733%22%2C%20composed%20by%20prolific%20American%20composer%20John%20Cage%2C%20is%20mainly%20comprised%20of%20what%20sound%3F",
"correct_answer": "Silence",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Farts",
"People%20talking",
"Cricket%20chirps"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20animal%20is%20featured%20on%20the%20cover%20of%20English%20electronic%20music%20group%20The%20Prodigy%27s%20album%2C%20%22The%20Fat%20of%20the%20Land%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Crab",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Fox",
"Elephant",
"Tiger"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20one%20of%20these%20Rammstein%20songs%20has%20two%20official%20music%20videos%3F",
"correct_answer": "Du%20Riechst%20So%20Gut",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Du%20Hast",
"Benzin",
"Mein%20Teil"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20one%20of%20these%20Pink%20Floyd%20albums%20were%20also%20a%20movie%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Wall",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Dark%20Side%20of%20the%20Moon",
"Wish%20You%20Were%20Here",
"Animals"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Johnny%20Cash%20did%20a%20cover%20of%20this%20song%20written%20by%20lead%20singer%20of%20Nine%20Inch%20Nails%2C%20Trent%20Reznor.",
"correct_answer": "Hurt",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Closer",
"A%20Warm%20Place",
"Big%20Man%20with%20a%20Gun"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "May%2016th%20of%20every%20year%20is%20known%20as%20__________%20Day%2C%20named%20after%20a%20punk%20band%20prominent%20in%20the%201990s.",
"correct_answer": "Lagwagon",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Goldfinger",
"Less%20Than%20Jake",
"Lit"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20French%20electronic%20music%20producer%20Madeon%27s%202015%20debut%20studio%20album%3F",
"correct_answer": "Adventure",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20City",
"Icarus",
"Pop%20Culture"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20relationship%20between%20the%20band%20members%20of%20American%20rock%20band%20King%20of%20Leon%3F",
"correct_answer": "Brothers%20%26%20cousins",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Childhood%20friends",
"Former%20classmates",
"Fraternity%20house%20members"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20a%20name%20of%20an%20album%20released%20by%20American%20rapper%20Pitbull%3F",
"correct_answer": "Welcome%20to%20Miami",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Dale",
"Global%20Warming",
"Armando"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20title%20of%20Sakamoto%20Kyu%27s%20song%20%22Ue%20o%20Muite%20Arukou%22%20%28I%20Look%20Up%20As%20I%20Walk%29%20changed%20to%20in%20the%20United%20States%3F",
"correct_answer": "Sukiyaki",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Takoyaki",
"Sushi",
"Oden"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20Brian%20May%27s%20guitar%20called%3F",
"correct_answer": "Red%20Special",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Blue%20Special",
"Green%20Special",
"Yellow%20Special"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20country%20does%20the%20electronic%20music%20duo%20%22The%20Knife%22%20originate%20from%3F",
"correct_answer": "Sweden",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Finland",
"Denmark",
"Norway"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20last%20song%20on%20the%20first%20Panic%21%20At%20the%20Disco%20album%3F",
"correct_answer": "Build%20God%2C%20Then%20We%27ll%20Talk",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Nails%20for%20Breakfast%2C%20Tacks%20for%20Snacks",
"I%20Write%20Sins%20Not%20Tragedies",
"Lying%20Is%20The%20Most%20Fun%20A%20Girl%20Can%20Have%20Without%20Taking%20Her%20Clothes%20Off"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20first%20track%20on%20Kanye%20West%27s%20808s%20%26%20Heartbreak%3F",
"correct_answer": "Say%20You%20Will",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Welcome%20to%20Heartbreak",
"Street%20Lights",
"Heartless"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20is%20the%20lead%20singer%20of%20The%20Lumineers%3F",
"correct_answer": "Wesley%20Schultz",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jeremiah%20Fraites",
"Jay%20Van%20Dyke",
"Neyla%20Pekarek"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20bands%20is%20Tom%20DeLonge%20not%20a%20part%20of%3F",
"correct_answer": "%2B44",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Box%20Car%20Racer",
"Blink-182",
"Angels%20%26%20Airwaves"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20members%20are%20in%20the%20Japanese%20rock%20band%20SCANDAL%3F",
"correct_answer": "4",
"incorrect_answers": [
"5",
"2",
"18"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20rapper%20had%20an%20album%20that%20went%20double%20platinum%20with%20no%20features%3F",
"correct_answer": "J.%20Cole",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Kendrick%20Lamar",
"Drake",
"Big%20Sean"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20rapper%20Drake%27s%20real%20name%3F",
"correct_answer": "Aubrey%20Graham",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Shaun%20Carter",
"Dwayne%20Carter",
"Andre%20Young"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20album%20by%20American%20rapper%20Kanye%20West%20contained%20songs%20such%20as%20%22Love%20Lockdown%22%2C%20%22Paranoid%22%20and%20%22Heartless%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "808s%20%26%20Heartbreak",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Late%20Registration",
"The%20Life%20of%20Pablo",
"Graduation"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20performed%20the%20guitar%20solo%20on%20Michael%20Jackson%27s%20hit%20%22Beat%20It%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Eddie%20Van%20Halen",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Steve%20Vai",
"Kirk%20Hammett",
"Zakk%20Wylde"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20released%20the%201991%20album%20%22Out%20of%20Time%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "R.E.M.",
"incorrect_answers": [
"U2",
"Coldplay",
"The%20Rolling%20Stones"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20Johns%20was%20murdered%20by%20gunshots%20outside%20the%20Dakota%20in%20New%20York%20in%201980%3F",
"correct_answer": "John%20Lennon",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Johnny%20Thunders",
"John%20Denver",
"John%20Cascella"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20novelty%20band%20was%20best%20known%20for%20their%20UK%20chart%20hits%20%22Combine%20Harvester%22%20and%20%22I%20Am%20a%20Cider%20Drinker%22%20in%201976%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Wurzels",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Goldie%20Lookin%20Chain",
"Bonzo%20Dog%20Doo-Dah%20Band",
"The%20Firm"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20was%20walking%20like%20an%20Egyptian%20in%201981%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%20Bangles",
"incorrect_answers": [
"R.E.M.",
"The%20Ocean%20Blue",
"The%20Connells"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Rick%20Astley%27s%20hit%20song%20%22Never%20Gonna%20Give%20You%20Up%22%20was%20released%20in%20what%20year%3F",
"correct_answer": "1987",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1985",
"1986",
"1988"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20was%20Britney%20Spears%27%20debut%20single%3F",
"correct_answer": "...Baby%20One%20More%20Time",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Oops%21...%20I%20Did%20It%20Again",
"%28You%20Drive%20Me%29%20Crazy",
"Toxic"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20artist%20curated%20the%20official%20soundtrack%20for%20%22The%20Hunger%20Games%3A%20Mockingjay%20-%20Part%201%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lorde",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Kanye%20West",
"Tove%20Lo",
"Charli%20XCX"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20was%20Bon%20Iver%27s%20debut%20album%20released%20in%202007%3F",
"correct_answer": "For%20Emma%2C%20Forever%20Ago",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Bon%20Iver%2C%20Bon%20Iver",
"22%2C%20A%20Million",
"Blood%20Bank%20EP"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20album%20did%20Gorillaz%20release%20in%202017%3F",
"correct_answer": "Humanz",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Plastic%20Beach",
"The%20Fall",
"Demon%20Days"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "%22The%20Genius%22%20is%20the%20original%20and%20secondary%20name%20of%20which%20Wu-Tang%20Clan%20member%3F",
"correct_answer": "GZA",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Ghostface%20Killah",
"Ol%27%20Dirty%20Bastard",
"Raekwon%20the%20Chef"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20studio%20albums%20have%20the%20heavy%20metal%20band%2C%20%27Metallica%27%20released%20in%20the%20period%20between%201983%20and%202016%3F",
"correct_answer": "10",
"incorrect_answers": [
"7",
"9",
"12"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20Beatle%20wrote%20and%20sang%20the%20song%20%22Why%20Don%27t%20We%20Do%20It%20in%20the%20Road%22%20after%20being%20inspired%20by%20seeing%20two%20monkeys%20copulating%20in%20the%20street%3F",
"correct_answer": "Paul",
"incorrect_answers": [
"John",
"George",
"Ringo"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20not%20a%20song%20on%20the%20album%20Graduation%20by%20Kanye%20West%3F",
"correct_answer": "Waves",
"incorrect_answers": [
"I%20Wonder",
"Big%20Brother",
"The%20Glory"
]
},
{
"category": "Entertainment%3A%20Music",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20was%20the%20guitarist%20in%20the%20band%20%22The%20Doors%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Robby%20Krieger",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Eric%20Clapton",
"John%20Densmore",
"Jimi%20Hendrix"
]
}
]